# Ing. FRANTIŠEK ĎURANA



#### **Contact**

Address **Q** 

Zákysučie 1212, Krásno nad Kysucou 023 02, Slovakia

Email 🔀

durana.frantisek@gmail.com

LinkedIn in

Frantisek Durana

Personal website 🔼

https://duranaf.github.io/

## Languages

Slovak language C2 English language B2 German language B1

## **Extras**

Driving license – B
Teaching volunteer - <u>detinanete.sk</u>
Publications – <u>CESCG Paper</u>
Certificates – <u>Udemy ReactJS</u>
Honors – Cum Laude (<u>FIIT STU</u>)

## **Summary**

Web Developer specializing in ReactJS front-end development. Experienced with all stages of the development and life cycle of the application. Well-versed in programming languages and technologies including ReactJS, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, TypeScript. Skilled also in the back-end part regarding Node, REST, databases and in addition mobile development.

## **Skill Highlights**

- Front-End Development
- Back-End Development
- Complex problem solving
- Creative UI design
- Innovations
- Adaptability

#### **Experience**

Frontend (Full Stack) Web Developer - Dec 2020 - Present Accenture, Bratislava, Slovakia

Development of applications for the Management of railway wagons

- ReactJS, JS, HTML, CSS, Node.js, TypeScript, Jest, Bootstrap, Swagger, MySQL, Express, REST, UML, Json, Redis
- Agile methodology (SCRUM) Jira, Confluence
- International team (communication in English)
- Code reviews, Openshift, Git

Android Developer - Feb 2019 - Feb 2020

QBSW, a.s., Bratislava, Slovakia

Development of Mobile application for patients

- Kotlin, Java, Samsung DeX, Git, REST, Json, XML
- UI/UX design
- Agile methodology

Web and mobile software developer - Jan 2018 - Sep 2018

ANASOFT, Bratislava, Slovakia

Analysis, design and implementation of the system for Digital signature and blockchain

- Technologies: Java, Android, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, PHP, MySQL, BPML, UML, Json, REST, jQuery
- Responsibility for the whole lifecycle of the project

#### **Education**

Faculty of Informatics and Information Technologies, STU, Bratislava

- Master's degree Information technologies (2018 2020)
- Bachelor's degree Information technologies (2015 2018)